https://www.redhillsupply.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

Privacy and Cookie Policy
JavaScript seems to be disabled in your browser.
For the best experience on our site, be sure to turn on Javascript in your browser.
Home
ToolsAir ToolsAir Cut Off ToolsAir Die Grinder KitAir Die GrindersAir DrillsAir EngraversAir FittingsAir FlangeAir GrindersAir HammersAir Impact WrenchesAir Needle ScalersAir RatchetsAir RivetersAir Sanders Polishers and BuffersAir SawsAir Scraper KitsAir ScrewdriversAir ShearsAir Specialty ToolsAir Tire BuffersAir Tool CoversAir Tool Repair Parts KitsAir Tools DisplaysChisel RetainersCut Off ToolsEraser WheelLubricationElectric & Cordless ToolsChuck KeysCombo kitsContractor ToolsDie GrindersDrillsElectric & Cordless Parts & AccessoriesElectric RatchetsEngraversGrindersImpact WrenchesROTARY TOOLSSanders & PolishersSawsScrewdriversShearsHand ToolsBit holderBit SetsBitsCrimpers Cutters and StrippersDrive HandlesExtension SetsExtensionsFile SetsFilesHammersHand Tool DisplaysHand Tools Parts and AccessoriesKey SetsKeysMaster SetsNut Driver SetsNut DriversPicksPlier SetPliersPry Bar SetsPry BarsPunch and Chisel SetsPunches and ChiselsRatchet SetRatchetsScraper SetsScrapersScrewdriverScrewdriver SetsSocket AdaptersSocket SetsSocketsUniversal Jointsupholstery toolsWrench SetsWrenchesMeasurement ToolsAngle FindersBaseBrake MeasurementCalipersCylinder Bore GaugesDial IndicatorsFeeler GaugesLevelsMeasurement Tools Parts and AccessoriesMicrometersRulersSpecialty MeasurementSquaresStandardsTape MeasuresTorque WrenchesMotorcycle ToolsTool StorageBenches and TablesCabinetsCartsCasters and WheelsChestCombination SetsDrawer Liners and MatsHand Tool BoxesJob Site BoxesLockers and Side BoxesMisc AccessoriesSocket HoldersTool BagsTool Box Trays and PanelsWrench Racks HoldersVehicle Specialty ToolsAudio, Video, and NAV SystemsBatteryBody ElectricalBody Mechanical And TrimBody PanelBody Sheet MetalBrakeClimate ControlClutchCooling SystemDrive BeltsDriveshaft And AxleEmmission ControlsEngine ElectricalEngine MechanicalExhaustFuel InjectionFuel SystemInspectionLifting and Hydraulics Parts and AccessoriesSteeringSuspensionTire And WheelTransmissionVehicle Specialty Parts and AccessoriesVehicle SpecialtyVehicle Specialty Tools DisplaysLiftingBottle JacksClutch and Fly WheelCrane AccessoriesCranesEnd LiftsEngine StandsJack StandsLifting and Hydraulics Parts and AccessoriesLiftsPallet JacksPorta PowerspressesPumpsRamsService Jackstransmission jacksTruck RampsUnder Hoist StandWheel DollysWinches & HoistsAir WinchesClassic Winch SeriesForce 5 Infinity Air Winch SeriesLiftstar Air Winch SeriesPullstar Air Winch SeriesThird Generation Air Winch SeriesAbrasives & CuttingAbrasivesBristle DiscsCut Off WheelsFlap WheelsGrinding BursGrinding DiscsGrinding PointsGrinding WheelsSand PaperSanding BeltSanding BoardsSanding PenSurface Prep Disc HolderSurface Prep Disc HolderSurface Prep DiscsWire BrushesSanding PadsScuff PadsCutting ToolsCutting Tool Parts & AccessoriesDrill Bit SetsDrill Bit SharpenerDrill BitsExtractor SetsExtractorsHole Cutters ArborsHole Cutters PilotsHole Saws and Hole CuttersIndividual DiesIndividual TapsKnives Saws BladesNut CrackersReamersTap & Die SetsThread Repair Chaser & InsertsThreading ToolsTube & Pipe CuttersKnives and CollectiblesGun CasesKnife SharpenersKnivesKnives and Collectibles Parts and AccessoriesKnives and Collectibles DisplaysMulti ToolsReplicasTactical ToolsToys and MiscWeldingElectrodes & RodsPlasma CuttersSoldering GunTorchesTorches HandheldWeldersWelding Parts and AccessoriesWelding Helmets and Replacement LensesWelding WireSafetyBody ProtectionBody WarmersBurn Protection Heat SleevesEye Wash and Drench StationsFirst Aid KitsGlovesHearing ProtectionRespiratorsShoes BootsShop Safety and Apparel Parts and AccessoriesShop Safety and Apparel DisplaysVision ProtectionPandemic SafetyPaint & BodyAdhesivesAir SprayerAir Brush Kits and AccessoriesApplicatorsBacking PlatesBody FillerBody Hammer SetBody PanelBody PullersBody Sheet MetalBody SpoonsbonnetsBooth FiltersBuffing and Polishing PadsBuffing and Polishing ProductsCar Wash ProductsCaulking and SealantsCaulking GunsChainsClampsCoatingsCompoundsCream HardenerDoor ToolsFiberglassFiberglass RepairFrame MeasurementGlass CleanerGun HolderHand Riveters and KitsHeadlight Resurfacing KitHooksMaskerMasking PaperMixing Cups and LidsNib FilesPaint SuitsPaint and Body Equip Supplies DisplaysPaint and Body Equip Supplies Parts and AccessoriesPaint brushesPaint Drying CuringPaint ShakerPaint SticksPaint StrainersPaint Touch Up ProductsPaintless Dent Removal ToolsPaintsPinstriping TapePlastic Sheeting and Car CoversPressure PotPrimers and Rust ProofingRags Tac Cloths MittsRivetsSand Bead BlastingSanding BoardsSanding PadsSlingsSolvent RecyclersSolventsSound ReductionSpray GunSpray Gun Cleaning KitSpray Gun Cup AdapterSpray Gun CupsSpray Gun KitSpray Gun WashersStud Welders KitsTapeTrim and Molding ToolsUndercoating productsupholstery toolsWaxesWheel CoversWindshield ToolsWork StandLightingBatteriesBulbsFlashlightsFlood LightsLight reelsLighting Parts and AccessoriesLighting DisplaysParts AccessoriesWelding Helmets and Replacement LensesWork LightsA/C ToolsAC Adapters Fittings and CouplersAC Charging ScaleAC hosesAC Manifold Gauges and SetsAir Conditioning FlushAir Conditioning Parts and AccessoriesClutch Hub ToolsCooling System AdaptersCooling System TestersFlaring KitsFluid Service MachinesFlushing Equipment SuppliesHose and Tubing ToolsHybrid OilIdentification EquipmentLeak Detection ElectricO Ring KitsOrifice Repair ToolsRetrofitting KitTemperature ToolsUV Dyes Oils and accessoriesUV Leak Detection Injectors kitUV Leak Detection LightsUV Master Leak Detection KitVacuum Pumps and OilsValve Core Service Repair ToolsTacticalReloading EquipmentAutomotive Tools & EquipmentShop EquipmentElectronics and DiagnosticsAmp Meters & ProbesBorescopeBreakout BoxesCircuit TestersCode ReadersElectronic & Diagnostic Parts & AccessoriesInformational ReferenceMultimetersScan Tool Upgrades & AccessoriesScan ToolsSpecial Use TestersTachometersTest Leads & AdaptersTiming LightsPortable Battery Charge TestBatt Elect and Charging TestersBattery ChargersBooster CableBooster PacksCordless Battery ChargersGeneratorsPortable Battery Charge Test DisplaysPortable Battery Charge Test Parts and AccessoriesAir Compressorsair dryersAir FilterBench GrindersBlow GunsBrake Lathe AccessoriesBrake Lathe BitsBrake LathesBrooms Brushes and SqueegeesCargo LiftingChain HoistsCHEMICALSConsumablesCranes and AccessoriesCreeper AccessoriesCreeper SeatsCreepersdrain pansDrainsDrum DollyDrum Top PadsExtension CordsFilter CrushersFloor Surface CleanerFluid Containersfluid evacuatorsFuel DeliveryFunnelsGas CaddysGlue GunsGrease GunsHand TrucksHeadlight EquipmentHeat GunsHosesInduction HeatersInvertersMagnets and Pick Up ToolsMetering DispensingMirrorsOdor Elimination Systemsparts washersParts Washers and Accessoriespressure washersPullersReelsRegulators And LubricatorsSand and Bead BlastersshopShop Tools and Equipment Parts and AccessoriesShop Air Fans Heaters CoolersShop and Traffic MatsShop Tool and Equipment DisplaysSlide HammersStepsStrapsTables and StoolsTips and NozzlesTire ChangersAmmco Coats Hutchison Run Flat Servicetowels wipes cloths tissueVacuumsVises and AccessoriesWheel BalancersWinches
GSA
Home
Privacy and Cookie Policy
Privacy and Cookie Policy
This privacy policy sets out how this website (hereafter "the Store") uses and protects any information that you give the Store while using this website. The Store is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. The Store may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by letting us know using our Contact Us information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email us this request using our Contact Us information.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
Cookie NameCookie Description
FORM_KEY
Stores randomly generated key used to prevent forged requests.
PHPSESSID
Your session ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to view and edit their orders.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history, if you have asked for this.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
MAGE-CACHE-SESSID
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE-SECTION-INVALIDATION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-TIMEOUT
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
SECTION-DATA-IDS
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
PRIVATE_CONTENT_VERSION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
X-MAGENTO-VARY
Facilitates caching of content on the server to make pages load faster.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-FILE-VERSION
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-STORAGE
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
Privacy and Cookie PolicySearch TermsOrders and ReturnsAdvanced Search
Copyright © 2020 Red Hill Ventures LLC. All rights reserved.
